cityweekend.com.cn 2004-06-06

# City Weekend - Editorial Privacy Policy

City Weekend is committed to protecting privacy online. We believe that greater protection of personal privacy on the web will not only protect users, but also increase user confidence and ultimately their participation in online activities. At City Weekend, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information.

The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information.

Our site may contain links to other web sites. We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide links from our sites. You should check the applicable privacy policy of the web site sponsor when linking to other web sites.

**Information Which We Collect**

We may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your e-mail address, postal address, home or work telephone number. If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners may need -- to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example -- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information.

We may require you to supply us with personal information (demographic information such as average age, income, education, population data, zip codes) during a "registration" process online. We use this general information to aggregate information according to demographics, such as gender, geographic location, age, income or a combination of these or other demographics.

**Use of User Information**

We may perform statistical analyses of aggregate user behavior. This allows us to measure relative interest in the various areas of our web sites. Any information we collect is used for its own internal purposes to improve the content of the web sites, to enhance users' experiences when visiting our site ****in terms of content and/or layout of our pages, and to provide the services required by an individual user. We do not use personal identifying information for any reason that is not disclosed either in this Policy or at the time the information is requested. We never send e-mail to you unless you request a particular service, or consent to being contacted by e-mail. There are instances where you will have the opportunity to subscribe to an e-mail list that will send information about the site or our advertisers to your e-mail address, but this will be done only with your permission and consent

**Third Party Access to Information**

We do not share personal identifying information with any third party without your permission. In some instances, we operate shared web sites with businesses affiliated with us. Our privacy policy will apply to these web sites, and our affiliates adhere to our privacy policy and will not share personal information with any third party without your permission. 

**Accuracy of User Information**

In order to ensure the accuracy of personal information provided for e-mail update registration, you may return to the registration form online in order to change information you have provided at any time. Questions regarding our privacy policy can be e-mailed to [editor@cityweekend.com.cn](mailto:editor@cityweekend.com.cn).

**Security of Information**

We use our best efforts to ensure the security of personal information submitted by users. When we collect information from our users, it is stored in an area where a designated City Weekend employee has access to it. The public will never have access to this information.

**Opt-out**

At any time while assessing our site, user while online may "opt-out" of further e-mail contact from us. This can be done by e-mailing [editor@cityweekend.com.cn](mailto:editor@cityweekend.com.cn). 

**The use of our material**

The right to download and store or output the materials in our site is granted for the user's personal use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without the express written permission of us is strictly prohibited. Users wishing to obtain permission to reprint or reproduce any materials appearing on these sites may contact us at [editor@cityweekend.com.cn](mailto:editor@cityweekend.com.cn).
